Erin Du

Programmer for **Web** and **Games**. Passion for problem solving. **4+ years experience on backend Java** for web application and **1 year diploma about Game Programming** at Vancouver Film School. Vancouver, BC (778) 302-4631 xiaodu321@gmail.com https://erinduxiao.github.io

EXPERIENCE

Super Neon Colosseum - UE4, C++, Multiplayer hovercraft shooter game - Networking Programmer - Team of 6

Summer 2017, Vancouver Film School, Vancouver, Canada.

- <u>Networking Programmer</u> Implemented features that related to multiplayer. Hosting and joining a session, character selection, respawning, score counting, player ranking and replication.
- <u>Data Visualization</u> Created a web-based tool to show heatmaps of the player movement data to help designers analyzing it.

Car DB Input Tool - WPF, C#, In-house windows application, Sub-lead programmer, Team of 5

2015 - 2016, Lifebox, Tokyo, Japan.

- <u>Sub lead programmer</u> Supported lead programmer, managed 3
 junior programmers to design UI, RDB and coding a windows
 application for a car lease company to input complex data of cars.
- Web application programmer Worked for a job searching web service which has modern development environment such as ticket driven workflow, auto build system from GitHub to AWS. I have added some searching keyword for the service, and learned the idea of how to make full text search with Apache Solr.

Online Payment Web Service, - Struts, Java, Frontend and Backend programmer, Team of 7 to 20

2012 - 2015, Yamato System Development Co., Ltd., Tokyo, Japan.

- <u>Security Programmer, QA</u> Implemented and designed tests for preventing it from vulnerability such as XSS, SQL injection, session fixation for an online payment service to keep security standard for credit cards, PCIDSS.
- <u>Web application programmer</u> Implemented API, OAuth, Refund features for the online payment service. Designed backend batch, which relates payment data to delivery data using COBOL.

EDUCATION

Vancouver Film School, Vancouver, Canada — Diploma

Feb 2017 - Feb 2018

Programming for Games, Web + Mobile.

Sophia University, Tokyo, Japan — Bachelor of Arts

Apr 2008 - Mar 2012

Japanese Language and Literature.

SKILLS

Frontend Development

HTML5, CSS, JavaScript(ES5, ES6), Ajax, AngularJS, jQuery, Bootstrap 3-4,

Backend Development

Java Servlet , JSP, Struts 1-2 Python , Django, Backend Batch design, SQL , NoSQL , Oracle , MySQL, Apache Solr

Game Development

C++, Unreal Engine 4, C#, Unity, VR, JavaScript, Box2dWeb

Etc...

Secure Programming for Web UML design (Sequence diagram, ER model), WPF, Redmine, Selenium, jUnit, Jenkins, Perforce, CVS, SVN, Git, Bash, VBA, windows bat

LANGUAGES

English - Professional Japanese - Native Chinese - Native

PASSION

Programming

 Helping people or with programming motivate myself

Seeing arts

- Going to musium

Reading

- Classic, History,
 Fantasy, SciFi
- Novels, Mangas